http://www.algarvepackage.com/privacy-policy/

Shopping Cart
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
At Tee Times Golf agency, we understand the importance of privacy and are committed to earning the trust of our guests by adopting high standards for the protection of personal information.
Information Collected:
If you wish to enquire/book with TeeTimes Golf Agency, we ask for some personal details. These details may include your name, address, email & telephone number.We may also ask you whether you would like to receive promotional emails and mailings from us about our other products or services or from other companies about their products and services which may be of interest to you.If you would like to revise the information provided to us, or feel what we currently have on record is incorrect, you may update the information by emailing info@teetimes.pt.We may from time to time ask you for further information in order to update our records or for particular purposes. You will always be informed how we will use any further information received from you.
Log Files:
When visiting our web site a log file is generated. This contains information such as the user's IP (Internet Protocol) address, how long that user spent on the site and which parts of it they looked at. We collect this information to help us diagnose problems and administer our systems, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site (e.g. what part of the world users are connecting from, or what ISPs are being used).We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that you remain anonymous even though we include your IP address in our aggregate information.
Cookies:
A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables our website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you donâ€™t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.We use cookies and Google Analytics tracking to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs and improve users experience. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Managing Your Personal Information:
At Tee Times Golf Agency we respect our client's privacy rights.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We do not buy or sell contact information.
How We Protect Information:
We implement a variety of hardware, software and workflow security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.
Surveys, Competitions and Promotions:
From time to time we conduct surveys, competitions and promotions and may request information from you as part of these. Participation in these is entirely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose any information which might be required.
Email / Newsletters:
As part of the registration process for our e-newsletter and/or enquiries, we collect personal information such as your name and email. We use that personal data to send you requested information regarding our services and to keep you updated on our golf initiatives and special promotions. You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link or by emailing us at reception@teetimes.pt
Loyalty Card:
Agree to receive our communications via email, newsletters and special promotions.
Correction/Updating Personal Information:
If your personal information changes or if you no longer wishes to subscribe, we will endeavour to correct, update or remove the personal data provided to us.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy:
Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check it periodically.We reserve the right to update our privacy policy posted on this page without prior notice.
This policy was last updated on 25th May 2018.
×
×
Hotels & Golf Holidays in
Lisbon
Porto
Madeira
Azores
Spain
×
Please fill this form to proceed.
proceed
No times for this date! Please change date.
Cancel
Confirm
×
COVID-19 - Safety Procedures:Booking in advance is compulsory.Clubhouse - mandatory the use of protective mask inside.Buggies can only be shared by family members or close friends.Flags cannot be removed or touched.Bunkers - no rakes will be available, smooth the surface with a golf club or your feet.Score cards should not be exchanged between players.According to our prestigious partners, golf courses and hotels, all new reservations that may be canceled for reasons related to Covid-19 will be fully refunded.
×
Our Christmas Gift60€for your next booking.Grab it here!
Register Now
